[{"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I thought that I had gained my cockatiel 's trust , but now he 's not coming to me when I open his cage .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"open\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"Grand - standing is ignored .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"ignored\", does the participant \"standing\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"Linda Robertson says they should be charged to Jim Steffes ' cost center , etc .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"charged\", does the participant \"they\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Exxon Mobil released nonessential staff from two giant Texas plants .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"released\", does the participant \"staff\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"We respect the fact that debate and discussion continue in many of our religious communities as to the scriptural , theological and liturgical issues involved .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"continue\", does the participant \"debate\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"They had a room with a $ 99 rate , which I booked .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"booked\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Rumsfeld , Wolfowitz and Feith staffed the CPA with Neoconservatives , most of whom had no administrative experience , no Arabic , and no respect for Muslim culture ( or knowledge about it ) .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"staffed\", does the participant \"Rumsfeld\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"I loved the atmosphere here and the food is good , however the tables are so close together that it feels very cramped .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"loved\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"The Ten Degree Channel divides the Andamans , which are the larger and more heavily populated northern islands , from the 20 or so Nicobar Islands in the south .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"divides\", does the participant \"Channel\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"\" ( China ) could be the second country to do that , \" Pike said .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"said\", does the participant \"Pike\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"Some board members pushed to have Winter removed , but there were concerns such action would lead to more chaos , the governor 's spokesman Maviglio said .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"removed\", does the participant \"Winter\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"We have and will have children of our own , grandchildren too .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"have\", does the participant \"children\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Security in the hotel seemed to be excellent , but we were never given an explanation as to why someone would open these items .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"open\", does the participant \"someone\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"China launches its second manned spaceflight mission\"\nQuestion: In the event \"launches\", does the participant \"mission\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"At least one expert believes China 's intentions might include a surprise attempt to circle the moon with astronauts before NASA 's planned lunar return .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"include\", does the participant \"intentions\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"As concerned citizens we affirm the liberty of adults of the same gender to love and marry .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"affirm\", does the participant \"we\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"The mysterious RAPHAEL Holinshed was named for the mysterious Neoplatonic Italian painter RAPHAEL Sanzio who painted _ St. George Fighting the Dragon _ ( 1504 - 06 )\"\nQuestion: In the event \"named\", does the participant \"Holinshed\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"These animals have the misfortune to produce a substance that is useful in the manufacture of perfume .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"have\", does the participant \"animals\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"The wedding had to be postponed as family members fled the outbreak of the war , she said .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"fled\", does the participant \"members\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"I survived it without a problem .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"survived\", does the participant \"it\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"Attached are my resume and an addendum covering academic & consulting experience .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"Attached\", does the participant \"resume\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"US - trained Malaysian biochemist Yazid Sufaat met with 9/11 plotters and two hijackers in January 2000 .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"met\", does the participant \"Sufaat\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"I used my card to purchase a meal on the menu and the total on my receipt was $ 8.95 but when I went on line to check my transaction it show $ 10.74 .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"purchase\", does the participant \"meal\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"We sued Houston Casualty last year but I do n't recall making any bad faith claims .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"sued\", does the participant \"Casualty\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"The last I checked , the Satanists have a long way to go to catch up with the death and destruction dealt out by self - proclaimed ( though false ) Christians .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"have\", does the participant \"way\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"It is our belief that this compensation plan will produce some of the largest checks in network marketing history .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"produce\", does the participant \"some\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"We were told by a detective and asked to check our credit for anything unusual .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"told\", does the participant \"We\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"The problem with this argument is that Bush lacked the experience necessary to be president when he ran in 2000 , so this sort of cheap shot just hoists him by his own petard .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"ran\", does the participant \"he\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"I started this page to help with my boredom .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"started\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"I think it s only fair that nowadays every town should provide at least one halal cafe or restaurant and hopefully one day every British catering establishment will be halal .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"think\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I have a parakeet named Cookie . :P\"\nQuestion: In the event \"have\", does the participant \"parakeet\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"\" They 're just pushing them aside , \" he said .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"said\", does the participant \"he\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"They sell feed and milk bottles at the front and I recommend you buy lots .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"buy\", does the participant \"you\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"But today , I got a boy and realized that he is HUGE !\"\nQuestion: In the event \"got\", does the participant \"boy\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"And he earned 112 points in 1971 - 1972 .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"earned\", does the participant \"he\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"They came to my house in no time and started working on the gate .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"came\", does the participant \"They\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"According to some reports , Zawahiri is thought by intelligence to be somewhere near the border of Pakistan and Afghanistan .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"thought\", does the participant \"Zawahiri\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"Even my PA i went to the other day said \" it must by comforting to have gone to a heart surgeon like him who will do nothing for you \" .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"said\", does the participant \"PA\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"I graduate in the spring , and so we 'd like to go between then and winter .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"graduate\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"\" The governor believes it was the defining moment , when what was a mounting problem turned into an instant crisis , \" Maviglio said .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"said\", does the participant \"Maviglio\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"In Baghdad Kadhim Talal Husain , assistant dean at the School of Education at Mustansiriyah University , was assassinated with his driver in the Salikh district .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"assassinated\", does the participant \"Husain\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"He told me \" no problem , we will match the offer or do better . \"\"\nQuestion: In the event \"match\", does the participant \"we\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"She asked for the dinner combo and they gave her two dinner plates instead .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"asked\", does the participant \"She\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"I recommend this company to ANYONE and everyone that needs great work done at a reasonable rate !\"\nQuestion: In the event \"recommend\", does the participant \"company\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"I have a cat named GummiBear , so no , R2D2 is not a stupid name .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"have\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"We need to change the lock and place posted signs at the gate .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"place\", does the participant \"signs\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"I MAKE MONEY NOT DEAL WITH BROKERS \" Wow , can you believe in today s tough times this dealership would be looking for any way to move vehicles .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"MAKE\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"He refused to believe them and ordered the military to win the war within two to three years ( before the next election in 1968 ) .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"believe\", does the participant \"them\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I tried to do it on the HRonline web - site , but the procedure is too complicated .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"tried\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"We felt we made it better because it introduced a process for review and refund . \"\"\nQuestion: In the event \"introduced\", does the participant \"process\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"He makes some good observations on a few of the pic's .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"makes\", does the participant \"He\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I expect to send them out to you sometime tomorrow .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"expect\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"Enron continues to feel free to move me around at will .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"move\", does the participant \"me\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"I have a Nacho Libre question .?\"\nQuestion: In the event \"have\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"My goal , however optimistic , is to execute the risk policy by the end of today .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"execute\", does the participant \"policy\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"Last June , an international initiative led by Japan to persuade the LTTE to come back to the negotiating table failed despite an aid package offer of US$ 4.5 billion .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"failed\", does the participant \"initiative\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"I expect to send them out to you sometime tomorrow .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"expect\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I have a cat named GummiBear , so no , R2D2 is not a stupid name .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"have\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"It has two parts , both of which are timed for 90 seconds each and the differential between the resulting two scores determines the likelihood of having a learning disability or attention deficit disorder .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"timed\", does the participant \"both\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"I detect the hissing lisp of the lying serpent in this article .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"detect\", does the participant \"lisp\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I promise you that if you follow the directions exactly that you will start making more money than you thought possible by doing something so easy !!\"\nQuestion: In the event \"promise\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"I have to mention that i recently separated the father into another cage close to the ' nest cage ' because he and the mother were fighting .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"fighting\", does the participant \"he\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"( News assistant Bobby Bender recalls the letter containing the items to have been addressed to The Sun . )\"\nQuestion: In the event \"recalls\", does the participant \"letter\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"She said a shower would be grand .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"said\", does the participant \"She\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"In short , China has the American economy by the throat .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"has\", does the participant \"China\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"It 's located in the huge HONKA Log Homes building , by Walmart off of Evergreen Parkway .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"located\", does the participant \"It\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Bush did no such thing .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"did\", does the participant \"Bush\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"Last June , an international initiative led by Japan to persuade the LTTE to come back to the negotiating table failed despite an aid package offer of US$ 4.5 billion .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"failed\", does the participant \"initiative\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"Clinton tried , and tried hard .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"tried\", does the participant \"Clinton\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"In response to the rockets , Israel resumed its policy of targeting militant leaders in air strikes .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"resumed\", does the participant \"Israel\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"I love the location and the apartment !!\"\nQuestion: In the event \"love\", does the participant \"location\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"he crawls on top of them but does not try to eat them .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"crawls\", does the participant \"he\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"They assumed a value -- unspecified -- for non-commercial species , and in doing so rendered the warming news a bit less rosy .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"assumed\", does the participant \"They\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"He explained that interrogations and other evidence revealed that Al Qaeda wanted to strike the US with a nonconventional weapon , most notably anthrax .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"strike\", does the participant \"US\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"The last wolf was killed in Yellowstone National Park in 1943 .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"killed\", does the participant \"wolf\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Newer semi-automatic wangs have a rail built into the receiver under the shaft .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"have\", does the participant \"wangs\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"The future president joined the Guard in May 1968 .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"joined\", does the participant \"Guard\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"i handle him every few days .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"handle\", does the participant \"i\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"** Google defies US over search data **\"\nQuestion: In the event \"defies\", does the participant \"Google\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"\" At some point , Patricia tripped or the bear tripped her and was at her back .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"tripped\", does the participant \"her\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"I tamed them in 4 days .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"tamed\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Today 's incident proves that Sharon has lost his patience and his hope in peace .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"lost\", does the participant \"patience\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"I love it .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"love\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"I like shrimp , fried , grilled , or steamed .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"like\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"THE DAILY STAR publishes this commentary in agreement with Agence Global\"\nQuestion: In the event \"publishes\", does the participant \"STAR\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"The information contained herein is based on sources that we believe to be reliable , but we do not represent that it is accurate or complete .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"represent\", does the participant \"we\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"I love this place lots of people to talk to and school is across the street !\"\nQuestion: In the event \"love\", does the participant \"place\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Joe removed a wasp nest for our condominium building and we appreciated the environmentally friendly method and prompt , friendly and informative service .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"removed\", does the participant \"nest\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"They assumed a value -- unspecified -- for non-commercial species , and in doing so rendered the warming news a bit less rosy .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"assumed\", does the participant \"They\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"He described Allawi 's face as that of a f*ed horse and he dismissed the whole government as a band of thieves and traitors .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"described\", does the participant \"face\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Allawi 's aged cousin and the man 's wife and daughter - in - law were abducted and guerrillas threaten to behead them if the Fallujah compaign is not stopped .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"behead\", does the participant \"them\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"Seth provides deep tissue massage which has significantly reduced the pain in my neck and shoulders and added flexibility and movement back to the area .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"provides\", does the participant \"Seth\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"The Ten Degree Channel divides the Andamans , which are the larger and more heavily populated northern islands , from the 20 or so Nicobar Islands in the south .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"divides\", does the participant \"Channel\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I doubt he will be extradited to Venezuela , which is the only way that question could be answered with a Yes .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"extradited\", does the participant \"he\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"The pictures are broadcast at a rate of about 60 Hz , which is how fast they need to move for us to see them as a moving , flawless picture .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"broadcast\", does the participant \"pictures\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"i agree , Hmmmmmm .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"agree\", does the participant \"i\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"They have a credit card minimum .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"have\", does the participant \"They\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"Abdel Rahman 's son was captured in Quetta , Pakistan in mid-February 2003 .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"captured\", does the participant \"son\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"His one - day mission vaulted his communist homeland into the elite circle of spacefaring nations - Russia and the United States - that can launch and sustain humans in space .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"vaulted\", does the participant \"homeland\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Only Irish coffee provides in a single glass all four essential food groups : alcohol , caffeine , sugar and fat .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"provides\", does the participant \"coffee\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"The wedding had to be postponed as family members fled the outbreak of the war , she said .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"fled\", does the participant \"members\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"Bradley 's record of 300 phenophases found that even prior to 1999 , spring was arriving in higher latitudes several weeks earlier than in the earlier years of her data .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"arriving\", does the participant \"spring\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"There are a lot of genetics at play between a Sussex and Silkie , so the offspring would vary in appearance .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"vary\", does the participant \"offspring\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"I found them and purchased both from a gallery in London , William Weston .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"purchased\", does the participant \"both\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"At one point they told me the dog had been fixed , the next day it had n't .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"fixed\", does the participant \"dog\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"The mind becomes strong and sharp .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"becomes\", does the participant \"mind\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"the guy came on time and did n't take any breaks , he went straight to work and finished the job efficiently and promptly !\"\nQuestion: In the event \"finished\", does the participant \"job\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"At the time , guardsmen were required to accumulate a minimum of 50 points to meet their yearly obligation .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"meet\", does the participant \"obligation\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Debbie said , it is going to be hard on me to sale my old dodge truck .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"sale\", does the participant \"truck\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"Climate : Humans fuss , animals adjust\"\nQuestion: In the event \"fuss\", does the participant \"Humans\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"But their parents refused to accept this .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"refused\", does the participant \"parents\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"The city mayor said rescuers were unable to retrieve the dead .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"said\", does the participant \"mayor\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"Last June , an international initiative led by Japan to persuade the LTTE to come back to the negotiating table failed despite an aid package offer of US$ 4.5 billion .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"failed\", does the participant \"initiative\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"I bought about half of the furniture I own from this place .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"bought\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"The poor quality starts at the receptionist desk , where the staff is very impatient and lack the efficiency I once loved about the office .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"lack\", does the participant \"efficiency\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"I have a Nacho Libre question .?\"\nQuestion: In the event \"have\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"I remain devoted full - time to the advancement of Firefox , the Mozilla platform and web browsing in general .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"remain\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"She had her cards memorized as well as everyone else s ( when you play you 'll see why you can know everyone else s hands ! ) .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"play\", does the participant \"you\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"I think this place is probably really great especially judging by the reviews on here .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"think\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"We felt we made it better because it introduced a process for review and refund . \"\"\nQuestion: In the event \"introduced\", does the participant \"process\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Some refused to leave , but so many were unable to .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"refused\", does the participant \"Some\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"There is a painting on my wall in the Oval -- first of all , I do n't know .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"is\", does the participant \"painting\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"they have their own website which you can easily find using any search engine .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"have\", does the participant \"website\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Most of the deals let you eat for 500 ff , and some of the deals are even free .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"eat\", does the participant \"you\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"The Ten Degree Channel divides the Andamans , which are the larger and more heavily populated northern islands , from the 20 or so Nicobar Islands in the south .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"divides\", does the participant \"Channel\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"I HAD TO ASK THE GIRL WHO BROUGHT MY FOOD AND SHE NEVER CAME BACK TO LET ME KNOW .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"BROUGHT\", does the participant \"WHO\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Several candidates were assassinated and targeted these last two weeks , others have been forced under threats to withdraw and to follow the example of the Islamic party .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"assassinated\", does the participant \"candidates\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"I doubt he will be extradited to Venezuela , which is the only way that question could be answered with a Yes .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"extradited\", does the participant \"he\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"Sheriff 's deputies in Louisiana made a third arrest Wednesday in the ongoing investigation of a case involving allegations of sexual abuse of children and animals at a Ponchatoula , La. , church .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"made\", does the participant \"arrest\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"These look fine to me .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"look\", does the participant \"These\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"I found this on a bulletin board and decided to try it : I do n't care about the useless pre-fabricated crap this message usually says .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"found\", does the participant \"this\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"As with so much climate research , not everyone agrees with these dire predictions .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"agrees\", does the participant \"everyone\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"It is this circle that makes sure that women remain inferior , that democracy is unthinkable and that exposure to the outside world is minimal .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"remain\", does the participant \"women\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"Nina Chahine , 19 , who with her family was among the named plaintiffs in the lawsuit , said her wedding in the southern city of Tyre was set for July 13 .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"said\", does the participant \"Chahine\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"They need to update the locker rooms ASAP .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"update\", does the participant \"rooms\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I ended up buying a birthday card and would probably come back for more .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"buying\", does the participant \"card\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"\" My first thought was to push it away , \" he said .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"push\", does the participant \"it\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"I had a sampler of IPA , Brawler , Love Stout & ESA .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"had\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I have 4 Golden Wonder Killifish .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"have\", does the participant \"Killifish\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"Climate : Humans fuss , animals adjust\"\nQuestion: In the event \"fuss\", does the participant \"Humans\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"\" At some point , Patricia tripped or the bear tripped her and was at her back .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"tripped\", does the participant \"her\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I love them .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"love\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"I have 5 sisters and so including my mom ... he is the only guy in a house of six females .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"have\", does the participant \"sisters\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"Kori told me she saw you last night at Steak Night and introduced herself since I failed to do so the last time we went .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"introduced\", does the participant \"herself\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"His one - day mission vaulted his communist homeland into the elite circle of spacefaring nations - Russia and the United States - that can launch and sustain humans in space .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"vaulted\", does the participant \"mission\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"The initial reservoir reports estimate reserves of 80 - 120 million barrels of sour crude and they estimate initial production to be 40,000 bpd starting in 1Q 2003 .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"estimate\", does the participant \"they\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"My last rabbit did that a few times , and he was fine ...\"\nQuestion: In the event \"did\", does the participant \"that\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"He needs more info about these trades ( i.e. , price info ) and would like to talk with you about it .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"needs\", does the participant \"info\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"<< Upon the sixth of April , Alexander the Great was born .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"born\", does the participant \"Alexander\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"Following on the heels of Ben 's annoucement yesterday , I thought I 'd post that I have joined Google as well .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"joined\", does the participant \"Google\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"In the meantime , we extend our best wishes for a safe and happy holiday season .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"extend\", does the participant \"we\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"I saw lots of videos about this , but actually it did n't help .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"saw\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"I love it .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"love\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"\" There have no business being there unless they are undermining Pakistan , '' says a Pakistani official .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"undermining\", does the participant \"Pakistan\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"China launches its second manned spaceflight mission\"\nQuestion: In the event \"launches\", does the participant \"mission\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"The first time I used them they arrived on time and towed car for me to the destination I needed .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"towed\", does the participant \"car\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I know that we address audit rights in the LLC agreement so this may not matter anyway if this is a right they already have .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"know\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"At one point they told me the dog had been fixed , the next day it had n't .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"fixed\", does the participant \"dog\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"Pioneers were assigned numbers , which were included on all cheques , enabling the campaign to keep track of who raised how much . )\"\nQuestion: In the event \"assigned\", does the participant \"numbers\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"To the north in Lebanon , there is serious debate within Hezbollah about entering the Lebanese political process in light of Syria 's promised withdrawal .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"entering\", does the participant \"process\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"I love them .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"love\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"Two vaunted economists - one a Nobel Prize winner and the other a nationally renowned budget expert - have analyzed the data at hand and put a price tag on the Iraq occupation .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"have\", does the participant \"analyzed\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I had a sampler of IPA , Brawler , Love Stout & ESA .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"had\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"We refer to licensed Fuel Cell Energy equipment .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"refer\", does the participant \"We\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"I was booked for 2 nights at this hotel in Oct 2007 .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"booked\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"The future president joined the Guard in May 1968 .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"joined\", does the participant \"Guard\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"We had a large party , about fifty people or so , and yet everything was served quickly and we all had a wonderful time .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"had\", does the participant \"We\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"She guided me through a very difficult period dealing with a family member 's suicide , coupled with elder abuse .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"guided\", does the participant \"She\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"None of them did , and most importantly , the winning bidders did not .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"did\", does the participant \"None\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"This little drip offered no apologies whatsoever , and even refused to give me the name of the manager until I pressed him for it 3 times .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"pressed\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"The only neurological sign that he shows is that he barely drags his toes and sometimes has trouble with his right lead .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"is\", does the participant \"sign\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"They have a credit card minimum .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"have\", does the participant \"They\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"The plants provide shade and root strength for bank stability .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"provide\", does the participant \"plants\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"I ordered a kid meal with a milk and found a bottle was half opened already .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"ordered\", does the participant \"meal\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I spoke with Jeff Hodge yesterday regarding the additional language from Peoples regarding Audit Rights .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"spoke\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"Fried rice has NO flavor , it literally taste like water .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"has\", does the participant \"rice\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"I know you are very worried , but getting her to the vet is the best thing you can do for her .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"know\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I took the original piece of metal and rigged it to make due since I had to complete the job .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"complete\", does the participant \"job\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"They have unbeatable price in town and deliver on time .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"have\", does the participant \"price\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"You need a background in law enforcement .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"need\", does the participant \"background\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"We had no choice but to stay but will take this as far as we can .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"had\", does the participant \"We\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"Grand - standing is ignored .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"ignored\", does the participant \"standing\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"We refer to licensed Fuel Cell Energy equipment .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"refer\", does the participant \"We\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I MAKE MONEY NOT DEAL WITH BROKERS \" Wow , can you believe in today s tough times this dealership would be looking for any way to move vehicles .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"MAKE\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"There are a lot of genetics at play between a Sussex and Silkie , so the offspring would vary in appearance .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"vary\", does the participant \"offspring\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"Anyway , after much yelling and cussing I hung up , grabbed a cab , and went to Geno 's .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"grabbed\", does the participant \"cab\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I recommend this company to ANYONE and everyone that needs great work done at a reasonable rate !\"\nQuestion: In the event \"recommend\", does the participant \"company\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"It incorporates Mr. Stojic 's and Mr. Kelly 's initial comments .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"incorporates\", does the participant \"comments\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"The bear dwarfed the 6 - foot - 1 Mr. Parenteau , knocking him to the ground , he said .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"dwarfed\", does the participant \"Parenteau\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I have a new born daughter and she helped me with a lot .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"have\", does the participant \"daughter\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"They provide an emotional infrastructure for atrocities .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"provide\", does the participant \"infrastructure\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"I have a kitten who just turned 3 months today .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"have\", does the participant \"kitten\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Barbara Walters did a story on gender roles in Kuwait several years before the Gulf War .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"did\", does the participant \"Walters\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"Peter Dale Scott includes an account of how Terrell 's whistleblowing was stifled by them in his book Cocaine Politics .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"stifled\", does the participant \"whistleblowing\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"I bought about half of the furniture I own from this place .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"bought\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"They took on the challenge of making my Ferrari all I dreamed of and more .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"took\", does the participant \"They\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"They asked us things that we would have never have thought of , and took extra time to meet with us when we needed it before the wedding .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"asked\", does the participant \"They\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"Tangipahoa Parish sheriff 's deputy Christopher Blair Labat , 24 , was booked Tuesday on one count of aggravated rape and one count of crime against nature .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"booked\", does the participant \"Labat\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I wanted to be very blonde and instead he pulled my root color throughout my whole hair which is a gross mousey brown .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"wanted\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"They both went to jail and a new manager was put in charge of the apartments .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"went\", does the participant \"They\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"A state Senate committee is set today to start serving 16 subpoenas on electricity producers and officials who manage California 's energy grid to determine whether they acted in concert to manipulate energy prices .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"serving\", does the participant \"subpoenas\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"They kept the name Oracle and created the RDBMS engine .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"kept\", does the participant \"They\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"\" At some point , Patricia tripped or the bear tripped her and was at her back .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"tripped\", does the participant \"her\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"I remain devoted full - time to the advancement of Firefox , the Mozilla platform and web browsing in general .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"remain\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"They love leaf or romaine lettuce and tomatos , celery , cucumbers , carrots .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"love\", does the participant \"lettuce\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"Nervous people make mistakes , so I suppose there will be a wave of succesfull arab attacks .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"suppose\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"I have to tell you that I have n't had one and do n't want one .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"have\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I saw lots of videos about this , but actually it did n't help .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"saw\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"The work was completed within one week , and everything was cleaned up on completion .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"completed\", does the participant \"work\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"A NATO spokesman said : \" There 's no tracking mechanism to ensure they do n't fall into the wrong hands .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"fall\", does the participant \"they\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"We love our new roof !\"\nQuestion: In the event \"love\", does the participant \"roof\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"Chahine said her immediate family spent about $ 20,000 to return to Detroit via Syria and Jordan .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"spent\", does the participant \"$\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"I have a parakeet named Cookie . :P\"\nQuestion: In the event \"have\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"The problem with this argument is that Bush lacked the experience necessary to be president when he ran in 2000 , so this sort of cheap shot just hoists him by his own petard .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"ran\", does the participant \"he\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"I had no problem with my delivery .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"had\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"I thought the UK was completely devoid of good NYC style pizza .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"thought\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Lo and behold , they replaced the screen ( which had to be ordered ) yesterday and did n't charge me a dime .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"charge\", does the participant \"me\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"She guided me through a very difficult period dealing with a family member 's suicide , coupled with elder abuse .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"guided\", does the participant \"She\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"All of the doors tend to look alike and having ' something ' on your door helps you and your kids find your room easier .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"tend\", does the participant \"All\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"The main reason I wrote this post is to ask anyone reading this if they know of some way I can help put a stop to this Cat Holocaust .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"wrote\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"I frequent this resturant on a weekly basis but usally only for lunch .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"frequent\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"Saddam killed every month more people than all those who died from suicide murders since the Coalition occupation of Iraq .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"died\", does the participant \"those\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I had a routine surgery for an ingrown toenail .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"had\", does the participant \"surgery\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"The 99 - tonne cache of AK47s was to have been secretly flown out from a US base in Bosnia .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"was\", does the participant \"cache\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"During his time in the Guard , George Bush flew the F - 102 Delta Dagger fighter - interceptor .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"flew\", does the participant \"Bush\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Wellywood looks rather cheap and tacky\"\nQuestion: In the event \"looks\", does the participant \"Wellywood\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"Just remember to make sure the mother is properly caring for the baby .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"caring\", does the participant \"mother\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"\" There is always the possibility they could jam us up , make us look like we are not numero uno , \" Pike said .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"jam\", does the participant \"us\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"This little drip offered no apologies whatsoever , and even refused to give me the name of the manager until I pressed him for it 3 times .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"pressed\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"Pioneers were assigned numbers , which were included on all cheques , enabling the campaign to keep track of who raised how much . )\"\nQuestion: In the event \"assigned\", does the participant \"numbers\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"I hope somebody understands what I mean\"\nQuestion: In the event \"hope\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Another problem is that sometimes bad eggs will fungus and the fungus will spread out and kill all the eggs .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"kill\", does the participant \"eggs\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"They assumed a value -- unspecified -- for non-commercial species , and in doing so rendered the warming news a bit less rosy .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"assumed\", does the participant \"They\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"I wish all happy holidays , and moreso , peace on earth .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"wish\", does the participant \"holidays\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I played dumb and asked him questions that I already knew the answers to and he responded with half truths and a few falsehoods .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"responded\", does the participant \"he\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"I had this ridiculous celebrity stylist from LA named Derrick .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"had\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"Reggie said he will pay us soon .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"said\", does the participant \"Reggie\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I have 4 Golden Wonder Killifish .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"have\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"Newer semi-automatic wangs have a rail built into the receiver under the shaft .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"have\", does the participant \"wangs\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"But there are strong hints in the country that a new Indo - Sri Lanka defense deal could be in the making .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"are\", does the participant \"hints\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Mike Indivero , I understand that Mr. Mike Croall 's release date from NEPCO is Oct 31 , 2001 .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"understand\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"Dignitaries condemn the act but visit her bereaved family and the money flows .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"condemn\", does the participant \"act\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"The S100 has a slightly larger screen and the new digic 5 processor .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"has\", does the participant \"screen\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Guerrillas threatened to assassinate Prime Minister Iyad Allawi and Minister of Defense Hazem Shaalan in retaliation for the attack .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"assassinate\", does the participant \"Allawi\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"He described Allawi 's face as that of a f*ed horse and he dismissed the whole government as a band of thieves and traitors .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"described\", does the participant \"face\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"Either I suck at my own style or Janice is a genius .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"suck\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"The salesperson refused !\"\nQuestion: In the event \"refused\", does the participant \"salesperson\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"As concerned citizens we affirm the liberty of adults of the same gender to love and marry .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"affirm\", does the participant \"we\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"At one point they told me the dog had been fixed , the next day it had n't .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"fixed\", does the participant \"dog\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"The money funds their travel , explosives , hideouts and permanent search for soft vulnerable targets .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"funds\", does the participant \"money\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"I expect to send them out to you sometime tomorrow .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"expect\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"Mike Indivero , I understand that Mr. Mike Croall 's release date from NEPCO is Oct 31 , 2001 .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"understand\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"The thing to do is to bring the right clothing with you , clothes so you can layer up if it is cold and take off layers when it warms up .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"layer\", does the participant \"you\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"Some conservationists want the protection extended so wolves can move into other states , including Colorado , Utah and Oregon , among others .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"want\", does the participant \"protection\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"I understand that we are still reviewing the attachment that lists the open transactions .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"reviewing\", does the participant \"we\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I like shrimp , fried , grilled , or steamed .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"like\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"Xinhua reports that a wide range of Iraqi political forces on Tuesday condemned Sharon 's murder of Sheikh Ahmed Yassin , a religious leader of Hamas , the day before .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"condemned\", does the participant \"range\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"I started this page to help with my boredom .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"started\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Sanctuary serves delicious , somewhat healthy food in a great restaurant / fast food style .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"serves\", does the participant \"food\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"We took our 7 month old and she laughed and giggled when ( very harshly I might add ) grabbing and ' kissed ' the goats and lambs .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"took\", does the participant \"We\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"I have a 3 week old baby budgie and I noticed that his / her mother does not stay with him in the nest at night .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"have\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Disney cruises offer 24 - hour room services , and the crews are ready to serve you the way you like .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"offer\", does the participant \"cruises\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"\" We applaud China 's space achievements , \" NASA spokesman Allard Beutel said Tuesday .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"said\", does the participant \"Beutel\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"I enjoyed the animations and wanted to share them with my friends .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"enjoyed\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I guess if you are someone not familiar with how NASA benefits our society I can see how one might form the opinion of yheggy - ga .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"form\", does the participant \"one\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"Rumsfeld , Wolfowitz and Feith staffed the CPA with Neoconservatives , most of whom had no administrative experience , no Arabic , and no respect for Muslim culture ( or knowledge about it ) .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"staffed\", does the participant \"Rumsfeld\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"Even my PA i went to the other day said \" it must by comforting to have gone to a heart surgeon like him who will do nothing for you \" .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"said\", does the participant \"PA\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I apologize for the following inconvenience , but I have decided to move this group to Yahoo , so that we can post files and photos and other useful things .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"post\", does the participant \"we\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"Just remember to make sure the mother is properly caring for the baby .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"caring\", does the participant \"mother\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"The dramatic increase in radiation - induced thyroid cancers in children and adolescents in Belarus , Russia , and Ukraine , which have been observed since 1991 , continues to this day .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"continues\", does the participant \"increase\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I promise you that if you follow the directions exactly that you will start making more money than you thought possible by doing something so easy !!\"\nQuestion: In the event \"promise\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"Following on the heels of Ben 's annoucement yesterday , I thought I 'd post that I have joined Google as well .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"joined\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"We 're set for 11/01/01 .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"set\", does the participant \"We\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I told Paul that you called him yesterday so abruptly because you did n't want to waste his time while you got tests done for arthritis .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"told\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"Above all , we need a total absolute unity and determination of the civilized world against all three circles of evil .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"need\", does the participant \"unity\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"Lee Huber made the same request last year and we gave her the chair ( she only wanted one , however ) .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"made\", does the participant \"Huber\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Two vaunted economists - one a Nobel Prize winner and the other a nationally renowned budget expert - have analyzed the data at hand and put a price tag on the Iraq occupation .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"have\", does the participant \"analyzed\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"In addition , is there someone who could consider the correlation between US CPI and the $ / euro exchange rate .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"consider\", does the participant \"someone\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"Peter Dale Scott includes an account of how Terrell 's whistleblowing was stifled by them in his book Cocaine Politics .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"stifled\", does the participant \"whistleblowing\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I thought that I had gained my cockatiel 's trust , but now he 's not coming to me when I open his cage .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"open\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"They picked my car up in Yarmouth and towed to Bath for a great price .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"picked\", does the participant \"car\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"We tried 4 different style of donuts , they were all the same when it came to quality .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"tried\", does the participant \"We\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I love it for discounted beauty items and household appliances .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"love\", does the participant \"it\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"Newer semi-automatic wangs have a rail built into the receiver under the shaft .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"have\", does the participant \"wangs\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"Nina Chahine , 19 , who with her family was among the named plaintiffs in the lawsuit , said her wedding in the southern city of Tyre was set for July 13 .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"said\", does the participant \"Chahine\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I need something reliable and good looking .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"need\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"He said Mr Dar , 33 , was arrested in Indian - administered Kashmir and belonged to the outlawed Lashkar - e - Toiba militant group .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"arrested\", does the participant \"Dar\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"These animals have the misfortune to produce a substance that is useful in the manufacture of perfume .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"have\", does the participant \"misfortune\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"They sell feed and milk bottles at the front and I recommend you buy lots .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"buy\", does the participant \"you\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"The Pakistani press reported that she was nabbed in Karachi after being spotted at the airport in late March or early April 2003 .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"nabbed\", does the participant \"she\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"'' It was the first time that Bush totally focused on the Taliban threat rather than Al Qaeda with the Pakistanis , '' says a Western diplomat .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"focused\", does the participant \"Bush\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"They have the best Egg Drop Soup I have ever tasted .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"tasted\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"** Google defies US over search data **\"\nQuestion: In the event \"defies\", does the participant \"Google\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"This means that messages initiated at Corp and intended for the entire Enron organization will not reach any business units outside the Corp domain .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"means\", does the participant \"This\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Rumsfeld , Wolfowitz and Feith staffed the CPA with Neoconservatives , most of whom had no administrative experience , no Arabic , and no respect for Muslim culture ( or knowledge about it ) .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"staffed\", does the participant \"Rumsfeld\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"I used my card to purchase a meal on the menu and the total on my receipt was $ 8.95 but when I went on line to check my transaction it show $ 10.74 .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"purchase\", does the participant \"meal\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"We live within 20 miles of the hotel and wanted to get away from our responsibilities for the night .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"live\", does the participant \"We\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"It is our belief that this compensation plan will produce some of the largest checks in network marketing history .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"produce\", does the participant \"plan\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"TEXAS ROADHOUSE HAS VERY GOOD MEALS , THAT THE MEAT COMES RIGHT OFF THE BONES .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"HAS\", does the participant \"MEALS\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"Al Qaeda had both the means and opportunity .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"had\", does the participant \"Qaeda\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}]